# **AMIT VERMA**

### **Frontend Developer**

**\$655568110** 

@ amitverma951994@gmail.com

Kurla West, Mumbai

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Senior Frontend Developer

#### Robinhood Insurance Pvt Ltd

iii 23-Jan-2018 to till date. Vikhroli West, Mumbai

#### Oneinsure OneGo

- The OneGo app is a unique platform that makes selling insurance a matter of a few taps on your phone screen.
- This app is developed on Ionic 3 framework, Angular 5

### **Oneinsure App**

- The OneInsure app lets you digitally store all your insurance policies and avail various services and support on them for a lifetime.
- This app is developed on Ionic 3 framework, Angular 5

#### Oneinsure SalesApp

- · This app is primarily useful for Sales & Upsell Teams to create to do list, understand client requirements, store client details, and monitor& manage daily/weekly/yearly tasks at various levels.
- This app is developed on Ionic 1 framework, Angular Js

#### **Chat Application**

- This app is bascially useful to communicate between teams and also use for support base.
- This app is developed on Firebase and Ionic 3 Framework, Angular 5

#### **Oneinsure Portal**

- Oneinsure portal is a web version where we can view policy and buy them.
- Oneinsure portal is developed on Angular Js

#### **SMS Application**

- This app is used to send auto sms from user device and it's mainly developed for Tellicallers Leads.
- This app is developed on Ionic 3 Framework, Angular 5

### Senior Frontend Developer

#### Travelibro Pvt Ltd

iii 1-Aug-2016 to 16-Jan-2018 

Mumbai Central - Tardeo, Mumbai

#### TraveLibro Website

• Travelibro is a social network where we can checkin and upload feeds and store our photos and videos.

### SUMMARY

Total work experience as a Software Developer is 4 years and 2 months in developing Websites, Hyrbid Applications.

1 years of experience on Ionic 3 Framework.

Technologies and Libraries hands on are Ionic 1, Ionic 3, Angular Js, Angular 5, Html5, Css3, Sass, Less, Graphql, Javascript, Jquery, Parcel Js as a build tool.

### **TECHNOLOGIES**

### Coding

**Open Project** 

Bootstrap	Javascrip	t Jquery
Ionic 1	Ionic 2 and 3	Framework
Angular J	s Angular	5 GraphQL
Version	Control	

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Web developer

math 17-July-2015 to 1-Aug-2016 Sion, Mumbai

- · Wohlig is catalyst that transforms the clients perspective of technology and empowers them to take advantage of the digital revolution that is constantly evolving.

## Wohlig Technology

Wohlig technology is a service based company.

# **EDUCATION**

# **BSC-IT**

KJ Somaiya Sci and Comm math 2013 - 2015 Vidyavihar, Mumbai

## **PASSIONS**

Dancing	 		 		
Rapping	 	 	 	 	
Cricket					